Finding Aid for Muschenheim, William. Architectural drawings and papers. 1925-1990
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Project Files
  - Job 7, Mrs. Felix Wilckes 1930-1942
    - [Mrs. Felix Wilckes penthouse apartment, 136 East 64th Street (New York, N.Y.). Remodeling. Alterations] 1937-1938, 1940-1942
      - Drawings, #. 00222-.00241 June 15, 1937-January 28, 1942, 20 sheets: various media; or smaller 60.5 x 103.8 cm.; 23-7/8 x 40-7/8 inches
        - [Ceiling fixture no. 9212 showing a dimetric view] / Kurt Versen, Inc. [Contemporary Lighting]., NYDA.1986.004.00236
          (Found with letter to Muschenheim from Kurt Versen, Inc., signed and dated July 23, 1937.)
        - Ceiling fixture no. 9212 [showing a F.S. cross section and longitudinal section]: Drawing no. 377-281 / Kurt Versen, Inc. [Contemporary Lighting]; drawn by H.K. 7/28/1937, NYDA.1986.004.00237
        - Trough lighting [showing a F.S. section]: Drawing no. 377-282 / Kurt Versen, Inc. [Contemporary Lighting]; drawn by: H.K. 7/28/1937, NYDA.1986.004.00238
          (Notes penciled in.)
        - [Lighting fixture no. 9031 showing a perspective sketch and a section] / Kurt Versen, Inc. [Contemporary Lighting] 1/2/1942, NYDA.1986.004.00239
          (Found with letter to Muschenheim from Kurt Versen, Inc., signed and dated January 1, 1942.)
        - [Lighting fixture no.9031SP. showing a perspective sketch and a section] / Kurt Versen, Inc. [Contemporary Lighting]; [drawn by] B.G. 1/12/1942, NYDA.1986.004.00240
          Found with letter to Muschenheim from Kurt Versen, Inc. signed and dated January 14, 1942.
        - [Lighting fixture no. 9031SP. showing] plan looking down at shelf, plan of reflector, [and 3 sections]: Drawing no. 421-161 / Kurt Versen, Inc., [Contemporary Lighting]; drawn by B.G. 1/28/1942, NYDA.1986.004.00241
      - Papers
        - Correspondence, bills: (Box A1, Folder 7-2)
          (Worked with the following people and companies: Kurt Versen Company, Mrs. Felix Wilckes ("Aunt Hedell [Hedwig]), H. Carmichael Smith (carpets), Howard and Schaffer Inc. (fabrics), Paul Scholze (cabinet work), among others. Among the correspondence is 3 letters to William Muschenheim from Hede Wilckes.)
        - Accounts: (Box A1, Folder 7-3)
          (various bills, certificates, order forms, and invoices. Material relates to alterations for the apartment of Mrs. Felix Wilckes. Worked with the following: Kurt Versen Co., Clark & Howes Inc., Francis Miller, H. Carmichael Smith, Paul Scholze, Thonet Brothers, Gunn & Latchford, J.G. Wilson Corp., Lustbader Upholstery Co., Carl Ber (painting), George S. Nichols Co., Gustav F. Wild, and others.)
        - Estimates: (Box A1, Folder 7-4)
          (worked with Kurt Versen Co. (lighting), Lustbader Upholstering Co., Paul Scholze (cabinet work, woodwork), Carl Berg (painter), The J.G. Wilson Corp. (blinds-sample included), and others.)
        - Archival, from Surveys (Box A1, Folder 7-5)
          (samples of materials, colors, and straw matting)
  - Job 8, William Muschenheim
    - [William Muschenheim weekend house (Hampton Bays, N.Y.). Plans, elevations and sections. Presentation drawings]
      - Drawings, #.00242-.00252 January 24, 1931-March 1932, 11 sheets 61.8 x 83.8 cm.; 24-3/8 x 33 inches
        This set consists of 5 pencil on tracing paper, 1 pencil and ink on tracing paper, 1 pencil and crayon on tracing paper, 1 blueprint on paper, 2 blueline prints on paper, and 1 blackline print on paper. J. Marshall, creator of 1986.004.00250 thru 1986.004.00252R is most likely "Jamieson Marshall" found in the archives concerning Marshall Unit Steel Framing-General Description.
        - [Axonometric view of house], March 1932., NYDA.1986.004.00242
        - Floor plan [showing furniture layout with measurements]: Drawing no. 1 March 1932, NYDA.1986.004.00243
          (. General notes given.)
        - [Floor plan showing electrical layout]: Drawing no. 2, [March 1932], NYDA.1986.004.00244
        - Foundation plan [showing soil lines to septic tanks and drain line]: Drawing no. 3, [March 1932]., NYDA.1986.004.00245
        - [North, south, east and west elevations; and a longitudinal section with measurements]: Drawing no. 4, March 1932., NYDA.1986.004.00246
          (Longitudinal section includes notes.)
        - Roof tier of steel beams [showing plan]: Drawing no. 5, March 1932., NYDA.1986.004.00247
        - Structural details [showing sections thru typical outside wall, terrace floor, typical end wall and tar roof, and typical uprights, all with measurements]: Drawing no. 6, [March 1932]., NYDA.1986.004.00248
        - [Isometric drawing showing Lupton steel frame construction], 12-24-31., NYDA.1986.004.00249R
          (Found in archival specifications folder "Marshal Unit System Steel Framing general description" with a penciled note "M see 299 Madison Ave.")
        - [Sketches of an elevation, plan and 2 details of an unidentified structure]., NYDA.1986.004.00249V
        - Marshall Unit Steel Framing [showing details of elevations and sections with measurements] / J. Marshall, February 20, 1932., NYDA.1986.004.00250
        - Marshall Unit Steel Framing [showing side wall section, interior section, end wall section and detail of exterior elevation with measurements] / J. Marshall, February 20, [19]32., NYDA.1986.004.00251
        - [Marshall Unit Steel Framing showing detail of plan and elevation(?) for beam placements, with measurements and a chart] / J. Marshall, March 4, 1932., NYDA.1986.004.00252R
        - [3 sketches of details related to steel framing beams(?)], NYDA.1986.004.00252V
      - Papers
        - Archives (Box A2, Folder 8-2)
          (Folder 1)
          (1 folder titled "Specifications and Details on the use and installation of Insulite...," consisting of 28 typed pages of specifications; 3 typed pages titled "Marshall Unit System Steel Framing, General Description," with 4 drawings of steel frame construction.)
  - Job 9, Architectural League (New York)
    - [Architectural League (New York, N.Y.). Galleries (display spaces). Competition drawings]
      ([Penthouse competition drawings exhibited at the Architecture League, 215 West 57th Street, New York, N.Y.] [competition drawings and floor plans of exhibition galleries])
      - Drawings, #.00253-.00255 circa 1931, 3 sheets: various media; or smaller 38.8 x 80.5 cm.; 15-1/4 x 31-3/4 inches
        This set consists of 1 blackline print on paper, 1 blueline print on paper and 1 pencil and ink on paper.
        - [Plan of first floor of exhibition galleries]., NYDA.1986.004.00253
        - Plan, elevation [and] section: Drawing no. 1. Copied from 1986.004.00256., NYDA.1986.004.00254
        - Plan, elevation [and] section: Drawing no. 1. Copied from 1986.004.00254., NYDA.1986.004.00255
  - Job 10, Cigar Store Ad
    - [Schulte Cigar Store, 44th Street and Broadway (New York, N.Y.). Design drawings]
      - Drawings, #.00256-.00257 circa 1932, 2 sheets: various media; or smaller 33.4 x 61.1 cm.; 13-1/8 x 24 inches
        This set consists of 1 pencil, ink, and watercolor (?) on tracing paper and 1 blueprint on paper.
        - [44th Street elevation, Broadway elevation and entrance plan]: Drawing no. 1., NYDA.1986.004.00256
        - [44th Street elevation and Broadway elevation]., NYDA.1986.004.00257
          (Copied from 1986.004.00256.)
      - Papers
        - Archives: (Box A2, Folder 10-3)
          (folder 1)
          (bills from A. Schulte & Co., and Contempora. Inc.)
    - [Webster Cigar display. Design drawings]
      - Drawings, #.00258-.00260 1935, 3 sheets: various media; or smaller 75.6 x 60.8 cm.; 29-3/4 x 24 inches
        This set consists of 1 photomechanical print with charcoal on paper, 1 charcoal on tracing paper, and 1 pastel on tracing paper. File 10 also includes a project for the Schulte Cigar Store, which has its own record.
        - [Portrait of Webster(?)]., NYDA.1986.004.00258
        - [Trace of a portrait of Webster(?)]. Traced from 1986.004.00258., NYDA.1986.004.00259
        - [Axonometric view of sign]., NYDA.1986.004.00260
  - Job 18, $1,000 House
    - [$1,000 House (location unknown). Design drawings]
      - Drawings, #.00261-.00264 1933, 4 sheets: various media; or smaller 44.1 x 34.5 cm.; 17-1/4 x 13-5/8 inches
        This set consists of 2 pencil and crayon on tracing paper and 2 pencil on tracing paper.
        - [Axonometric view of house and patio]., NYDA.1986.004.00261
        - [Floor plan showing furniture lay-out and patio]., NYDA.1986.004.00262
        - [Floor plan]., NYDA.1986.004.00263
        - [4 exterior elevations], NYDA.1986.004.00264
  - Job 19, 830 and 840 Park Avenue
    - [Penthouse, 830 Park Avenue (New York, N.Y.). Alterations]
      - Drawings, #.00265-.00267 May 1, 1933, 3 sheets: various media; or smaller 53 x 80.7 cm.; 21 x 31-3/4 inches
        This set consists of 1 pencil on tracing paper and 2 blueprints on paper. 1986.004.00266. and 1986.004.00267 were originally filed with drawings for Apt.'s 8A and 11B of the same address. Geo. [George] and Edw. [Edward] Blum, Architects address was at 415 Lexington Avenue and 505 5th Avenue during this project.
        - Preliminary plan [showing alterations to be made]: Drawing no. 1 May 1, 1933, NYDA.1986.004.00265
        - Proposed [floor plan]: Job #728, A35 / Geo. [George] & Edw. [Edward] Blum, Archts., NYDA.1986.004.00266
          (Blum's office address noted as 415 Lexington Avenue, New York, N.Y. Geo. & Edw. Blum were the original architects at 830 Park Avenue.)
        - [Floor plan showing individual rooms with their assigned numbers and occupant's names], NYDA.1986.004.00267
    - [Apartments, 830 Park Avenue (New York, N.Y.). Alterations]
      - Drawings, #.00268-.00270R March-June 1933, 19 sheets: various media; or smaller 63.3 x 71.7 cm.; 25 x 18-1/4 inches
        This set consists of 9 pencil on tracing paper, 5 pencil and crayon on tracing paper, 3 blackline prints on paper, 1 photomechanical print on paper, and 1 ink on tracing paper.
        - Plan of second floor / Geo.[George] and Edw. [Edward] Blum, architects., NYDA.1986.004.00268
        - [Typical floor plan]., NYDA.1986.004.00269
        - [Typical floor plan and separate floor plans for apartment types "A", "B", and "C"]. This is page 75 from the Douglas Elliman locator., NYDA.1986.004.00270R
        - [Typical floor plan and separate floor plans for apartment types "A", "B", and "C"]. This is page 75 from the Douglas Elliman locator., NYDA.1986.004.00270V
        - [Typical floor plan of apartment type "B" and key plan showing where Apartment "B" is located on the floor]., NYDA.1986.004.00271
          (Notes mark drawing in pencil and crayon for electrical lay-out.)
        - Plan [showing] alteration to apartment 11B: Drawing no. 1 / Lloyd Westbrook, architect; William Muschenheim, associated, February 22, 1933., NYDA.1986.004.00272
          (Rooms are labelled as a key for the specifications.)
        - Elevations and details [of] alteration to apartment 11B [showing west and east elevations of reception hall and living room with measurements, west elevation of dining room and section at stair landing with measurements, and 4 F.S.D.'s]: Drawing no. 2 / Lloyd Westbrook, architect; William Muschenheim, associated, February 22, 1933., NYDA.1986.004.00273
        - Details in room no. 2, [the reception hall, for alteration to apartment 11B, showing detail of solid jib and wood hand-rail looking up stairway, detail of solid jib and wood hand-rail between spaces 2 and 2B, F.S.D. section of brass bracket for hand-rail over sold jib, F.S.D. at top of book cases on east wall of room no. 2, and 4 other F.S.D.'s]: Drawing no. 3 / Lloyd Westbrook, architect; William Muschenheim, associated, March 3, 1933., NYDA.1986.004.00274
        - [Details of radiator enclosure for alteration to apartment 11B showing detail of radiator enclosure at west of space no. 3, F.S.D. of section of radiator enclosure at north of space no. 1, and 3 other F.S.D.'s, all with measurements]: Drawing no. 4, March 7, 1933., NYDA.1986.004.00275
        - Paint schedule [showing chart and keyed floor plan]: Drawing no. 5, March 11, 1933., NYDA.1986.004.00276
        - Preliminary plan [of] scheme for alterations to apt. B [showing] floor plan of N.W. space of apt., with rooms numbered and electrical layout]., NYDA.1986.004.00277
        - Scheme for alterations to apt. B [showing floor plan of N.W. area of apt.]., NYDA.1986.004.00278
        - Scheme for alterations to closets [for] apt. 11B [showing plan of N.W. chambers]., NYDA.1986.004.00279
        - Scheme for alterations to closets [in] apt. 11B [showing plan of N.W. chambers]., NYDA.1986.004.00280
        - Scheme for alterations to apt. B [showing east elevation of living room and reception hall, south elevation of living room, and west elevation of reception hall]., NYDA.1986.004.00281
        - [Cutaway drawing of an axonometric view of the north west space of apt. B]., NYDA.1986.004.00282
        - Plan [showing] alteration to apartment 8A: Drawing no. 11 March 21, 1933, NYDA.1986.004.00283
          (. Rooms are labeled as a key for the specifications. Drawing is mistakenly labeled Job no. 20.)
        - Elevations and details [of] alteration to apartment 8A [showing north elevation of living room space no. 1; east elevation of living room, east elevation of dining room, space no. 3; north elevation of reception hall, space no. 2; south elevation of reception hall; section thru space 1A showing shelves at west end; and 3 F.S.D.'s]: Drawing no. 12, March 21, 1933., NYDA.1986.004.00284
        - F.S.D. of hand-rail on north wall in space 2B [for] alteration to apt. 8A: Drawing 14, [1933]., NYDA.1986.004.00285
        - Paint schedule [showing chart and key floor plan]: Drawing no. 15, June 6, 1933., NYDA.1986.004.00286
          (Drawing is mistakenly labeled Job no. 20.)
      - Papers
        - Alt. to apts. 8A + 11B, 830 Park (Box A2, Folder 19-7)
          (folder 4)
          (1 copy of "The Little Red Book 1940," (small calendar with notes inside); 2 pages of handwritten notes titled "Preliminary list of proposed alterations to lobby at 840 Park Ave.")
        - 830 Park Ave., Specs., archival: (Box A2, Folder 19-8)
          (approx. 90 pages of specifications.)
        - Specs. 11B, 830 Park Ave., archival: (Box A2, Folder 19-9)
          (folder 2)
          (4 pages of specifications and estimates)
        - Specs. & Estimates, 8A, 830 Park Ave., archival: (Box A2, Folder 19-10)
          (folder 3)
          (3 pages of specifications and estimates.)
        - Contracts, orders, 11B, 830 Park, archival: (Box A2, Folder 19-11)
          (4 pages of contracts & orders.)
        - Prints photographs showing interior views, 3 items (Box A2, Folder 19-12)
        - contracts, orders, Apt. 8A, 830 Park Ave. archival: (Box A2, Folder 19-13)
          (folder 5)
          (4 pages of contracts, orders; 1 typed booklet re expenses.)
      - Photographs (Box B10)
    - [840 Park Avenue (New York, N.Y.). Alterations]
      - Drawings, #.00270V, .00288-.00294 January 22, 1934, June 20, 1940, 9 sheets: various media; or smaller 57.2 x 71.9 cm.; 22-5/8 x 28-1/4 inches
        This set consists of 3 pencil on tracing paper, 2 blackline prints, 2 pencil and crayon on tracing paper, 1 blueprint on paper, and 1 ink on tracing paper.
        - V. [Typical floor plan for apartment types "A" and "B"]. This is page 76 from the Douglas Elliman Locator, NYDA.1986.004.00270
        - [1st floor, north apartment, showing partial plan, partial elevation, and a section] / Louis A. Hornum, R.A., January 22, 1934., NYDA.1986.004.00287
          (Hornum's office was noted as 1181 Broadway N.Y.C.)
        - [Study and perspective view of entrance lobby], NYDA.1986.004.00288
        - Perspective view facing elevator: Drawing 1 6/20/1940, NYDA.1986.004.00289
        - Perspective view facing elevator: Drawing 1, 6-20-40., NYDA.1986.004.00290
          (Copied from 1986.004.00289.)
        - [Plan of (?) also showing markings for alteration], NYDA.1986.004.00291
        - [Plan of (?)]. This is the same plan as in 1986.004.00291 showing layout after possible alteration., NYDA.1986.004.00292
        - [Partial plan study showing foyer, kitchen, and servants dining rm.], NYDA.1986.004.00293
        - [Partial plan study showing foyer, kitchen, and serv. din. rm.], NYDA.1986.004.00294
      - Papers
        - 840 Park Ave., Lobby, archival: (Box A2, Folder 19-1)
          (correspondence with Douglas L. Elliman & Co. (real estate co.); list of proposed alterations.)
  - Job 20, William H. Labrot
    - [William H. Labrot, Esq. residence, 326 East 51st Street (New York, N.Y.). Alterations]
      - Drawings, #.00308-.00337 1931-September 10, 1940, 30 sheets: various media; or smaller 63.7 x 85 cm.; 25-1/8 x 33-1/2 inches
        This set consists of 11 pencil on paper, 8 pencil on tracing paper, 3 ink on tracing paper, 2 pencil and crayon on tracing paper, 2 ink on paper, 1 crayon on paper, 2 blueprints on paper and 1 blackline print on paper. I.S. was most likely Irving Scott, whom William Muschenheim worked with while under Joseph Urban.--from W. Muschenheim's Oral History.
        - [Survey, as in possession] / J. George Hollerith, June 11, 1931. Hollerith's address was at "176 B'way"., NYDA.1986.004.00317
        - [Stoop showing plan and section, with measurements] / Joseph Urban, Architect, August 5, 1931., NYDA.1986.004.00318
        - [Key floor plans showing basement, first and second floors with measurements and electrical layout, and schedules for floors and doors]: Sheet no. 1 / Joseph Urban, Architect; William Muschenheim, Associate; made by I.S. 7/29/1931 Top right of drawing is cut away., NYDA.1986.004.00308 R
        - [Plans of basement, first and second floors]., NYDA.1986.004.00308 v
        - [Plans of basement with yard, 1st and 2nd floors]., NYDA.1986.004.00321
        - [Plans of basement, 1st and 2nd floors]., NYDA.1986.004.00319
        - [Plans of basement, 1st and 2nd floors with typed room labels pasted on]., NYDA.1986.004.00320
        - Longitudinal section [with measurements, front and rear elevations, and 2 details of railing on rear extension roof]: Sheet no. 2 / Joseph Urban, Architect; William Muschenheim, Associate; made by I.S. and E.B. 7/29/1931 rev. 7/30/1931, NYDA.1986.004.00309
        - Plumbing diagram [and cellar plan showing drainage]: Sheet no. 3 / Joseph Urban, Architect; William Muschenheim, Associate; [made by I.S.], [1931]., NYDA.1986.004.00310
          (Also noted as P&D-1089-31.)
        - Details of dining room, space no. 13 [showing floor plan, plan of roof bulkhead, plan of radiator enclosure, section through radiator enclosure, elevation showing radiator, elevation showing staircase, and other section details]: Sheet no. 4 / Joseph Urban, Architect; William Muschenheim, Associate; made by E.B. and W.M. 07/29/1931 rev. 8/7/1931, NYDA.1986.004.00311
        - Details of bathroom, space no. 38 [showing plan, north, south, east and west elevations, and 2 F.S. details]: Sheet no. 5 / Joseph Urban, Architect; William A. Muschenheim, Associate; with rev. by E.B 07/29/1931 rev. 8/17/1931, NYDA.1986.004.00312
        - Details of living room, space no. 21 [showing elevation showing staircase, plan and section of fireplace, detail of stairs leading from 1st to 2nd floor, F.S. detail of door jambs at head of dining room stairs and 4 other detail sections]: Sheet no. 6 / Joseph Urban, Architect; William A. Muschenheim, Associate; made by E.B. and W.M., 8/3/31, rev. 8/17/1931, NYDA.1986.004.00313
        - [Details of 1st and 2nd floors showing plan, elevations and sections of entry doors and plan, section and elevation of stairs, including detail of handrail, with measurements]: Sheet no. 8 / Joseph Urban, Architect; made by W.M., August 18, 1931., NYDA.1986.004.00314
        - Kitchen and pantry cabinets [showing plans, elevations and detailed sections, with measurements]: Sheet no. 9 / Joseph Urban, Architect; made by W.M., [8/18/31]., NYDA.1986.004.00315
        - Color schedule [showing a table for painting of interiors, street facade, and the garden facade]: Sheet no. 11 / Josph Urban, Architect; made by W.M., NYDA.1986.004.00316
        - [Exterior elevations showing rear and front(?)]: Drawing no. 12., NYDA.1986.004.00322
        - [Exterior elevations showing rear and front(?)]., NYDA.1986.004.00323
        - [Exterior elevation of rear]: Drawing no. 13., NYDA.1986.004.00324
        - [Design of glass sliding door [showing elevation and 2 F.S.D. sections]: Drawing no. 14, October 7, 1933. Drawing has a hole in the upper left corner., NYDA.1986.004.00325
        - [Plan showing layout of furniture]: [15?]., NYDA.1986.004.00326
          (Drawing was found in folder labeled "Furniture lay-out" and Drawing no. "15".)
        - Designs of furniture and carpentry work for living room [showing elevation of bookshelves with built-in desk and 2 detailed sections, and isometrics [i.e. axonometric views] of a couch, table and shelf on the west wall]: Drawing no. 16, October 21st, 1933., NYDA.1986.004.00327
        - Upholstered chairs [showing elevation, and 2 axonometric views, with measurements]: Drawing no. 17, November 28th, 1933., NYDA.1986.004.00328
        - Vestibule [showing plan, east and west elevations and 2 detailed sections]: Drawing 18 09/19/1938 rev. 9/24/1938, NYDA.1986.004.00330
        - Floor design for vestibule [using rubber, showing plan] 9/21/1938 Drawing notes it as "study #19" to be "filed with Drawing #18"., NYDA.1986.004.00331
        - Detail of closet in vestibule [showing a plan]: Drawing 19, 9/24/1938, NYDA.1986.004.00329
        - [Partition and door in living room showing plan, elevations an F.S.D; and elevations of new tub and radiator grill in N.E. bathroom on the 2nd floor with measurements]: Drawing no. 20, 9/10/1940, NYDA.1986.004.00332
        - [Axonometric view of living room showing furnishings]., NYDA.1986.004.00333
        - [Axonometric view of living room showing furnishings]. Copied from 1986.004.00333., NYDA.1986.004.00334
        - [Axonometric view of living room showing furnishings]. Traced from 1986.004.00333., NYDA.1986.004.00335
        - [Interior perspective of living room showing staircase and bookshelves]., NYDA.1986.004.00336
        - [Interior perspective of dining room showing staircase]., NYDA.1986.004.00337
      - Papers
        - archival: (Box A2, Folder 21-1)
          (1 typed report titled "Specifications for Alteration to Residence for William H. Labrot, 326 East 51st Street, New York City, Joseph Urban, Architect, William Muschenheim, Associate... 11 23 pp.)
        - archival: estimates, contracts, bills. (Box A2, Folder 20-3)
          (Worked with: Gustav F. Wild (plate glass & mirrors), Tuttle & Bailey (heating & ventilation), Marshall Construction Co., Mrs. William H. Labrot (Eleanor), Stroheim & Romann (upholstery and fabrics), I.S. Pertofsky (metal works), Thonet Brothers (furniture), and others.)
        - Archival: (Box A2, Folder 20-4)
          (1 booklet containing specifications for "Standard" plumbing fixtures; 10 typed pages containing "general conditions" of the [contract?])
        - misc. (Box A2, Folder 20-7)
          (specs: 3 6X411 handwritten pages of specifications, and 1 8.5x1111 page of specs; 2 samples of material from "modernfold doors.")
        - archival: contract (Box A2, Folder 20-9)
          ("The A.I.A Short Form for Small Contracts," (between C.G. Flygare, Inc. and Mrs. Eleanor Labrot.))
        - prints, sepia prints showing interior and exterior views, 2 items (Box A2, Folder 20-11)
        - archival: (Box A2, Folder 20-12)
          (folder 6)